#${entry.rank}
#Channel
#channel-name
#name / #id
${data.error}
${entry.name}
${valStr}
&copy; 2025 Orbit Bot. All rights reserved.
&gt; Text
&gt;&gt;&gt; Text
&larr; Back to Dashboard
&lt;:name:id&gt;
&times;
**Text**
*Text*
, and
/10)
/5)
@User
__Text__
{count}
{id}
{mention} / {user}
{server}
{user}
{username}
||Text||
~~Text~~
+ Add Channel
+ Add File-Channel
+ Add Hub
+ Add Option
+ Add Reaction-Channel
+ Add Role
+ Add Trigger
0/2000
0/2048
0/256
0/4096
1. Acceptance of Terms
1. Information We Collect
2. Description of Service
2. How We Use Information
3. Data Storage and Security
3. User Conduct
300
4. Contact Us
4. Disclaimer of Warranties
500
Action
Action to take if the user fails to verify within a specific timeframe.
Activate the verification gate.
Add Field
Add Orbit in seconds. No credit card, no setup fees. Completely free.
Add Response
Add to Discord
Add User
Advanced Logs
AI Content Filter
Allow banned or muted users to submit an appeal via the web dashboard.
Allow Solo Counting
Allow the same user to count consecutive numbers in a row.
Allow users to create their own temporary voice channels.
Allow users to open support tickets.
Allowed Channels
Allowed Punishments
Allowed Roles
America/New_York
Amount added per streak day ramping up to the limit. If disabled, uses 80% of the combined work reward range.
Amount of XP per command.
Amount of XP per message.
Amount of XP per minute in voice channels.
Amount of XP per reaction.
Anonymous Moderators
Anti Caps
Anti Invites
Anti Links
Anti Spam
Anti-Alt
Anti-Alt Account
Anti-Bot Add
Anti-Link
Anti-Spam
Appeal Channel
Appeal Submitted!
Appeals System
as placeholders.
as placeholders. Use
Author Name
Auto Ban Channel (Honeypot)
Auto Leaderboard
Auto Mod
Automatic Leaderboard Channel
Automatically assign roles when a user joins. Set multiple roles at once.
AutoMod & Security
Auto-Reaction Channels
Auto-Replies
Auto-Rolle
Background Image
Ban
Ban User
Banned Words
Base Reward
Beautiful custom welcome images with custom backgrounds and messages for new members.
Bet Limit
Blacklist
Block messages containing specific words or phrases.
Blocked XP Channels
Blocked XP Roles
Bold
Boost Channel
Boost Count
Boost Messages
Boosts
Bot
Bot Adders (Anti-Bot Add)
Bot Manager Roles
Bot Managers
Bot Rollen
Bot Timezone
Bots
browse
By accessing and using Orbit, you accept and agree to be bound by the terms and provision of this agreement.
Cancel
CAPTCHA (Solve Image)
CAPTCHA or one-click verification to keep bots and alts out of your community.
Celebrate when members boost your server with a custom card or embed message!
Changes saved successfully!
Channel
Channel Automation
Channel Boosters (
Channel where level up messages are sent.
Channel where the leaderboard is automatically updated every hour.
Channel where the wealth leaderboard is updated hourly.
Channels
Channels where members earn no XP.
Charts for
Choose a server to manage its configuration.
Color of the automatic leaderboard embed.
Command Cooldown
Command Money
Command Money Amount
Command Money Enabled
Command Prefix
Command XP
Command XP Amount
Command XP Enabled
Command-Only Channels
Conditional Message
Content / Message Text
Cooldown in seconds between command rewards.
Cooldown in seconds between commands.
Cooldown in seconds between each stat count.
Cooldown in seconds between message rewards.
Cooldown in seconds between messages.
Cooldown in seconds between reaction rewards.
Cooldown in seconds between reactions.
Counting Channel
Create beautiful support panels with custom categories, auto-roles, and log channels.
Currency Symbol
Current Channel
Current Count:
Custom Emoji
Custom Leaderboard URL
Custom Prefix
Custom URL
Custom vanity URL for public leaderboard view.
Dashboard
Default Work Responses
Delete
Description
Design the embed that users will see when they need to verify.
Drag &amp; Drop image here, or
Earn money by sending text messages.
Earn money by spending time in voice channels.
Earn money when adding reactions to messages.
Earn money when executing bot commands.
Economy System
Edit Rule
Embed Color
Embed Message
Embed Message Color
Embedded Message
Embedded Message Name
Emoji
Enable Auto Mod
Enable Boost Messages
Enable Goodbye Messages
Enable Temp Voice System
Enable Tickets
Enable Verification
Enable Welcome Messages
Enforce consecutive number counting. Messing up locks the channel and resets count to 0.
Error loading leaderboard.
Europe/Berlin
Everything your server needs,
Excluded Channels
Excluded Roles
Executor In Logs
Exempt Roles
Exempt User IDs
Feld hinzufÃ¼gen
File-Only Channels
Fixed reward for day 1. If disabled, tier reward is used as a base for day 1.
Footer Text
Form
Full Block Quote
General
Give this role to users when they boost the server.
Giveaways & Polls
Global multiplier for all earned money.
Global multiplier for all earned XP.
Global Options
GOODBYE
Goodbye Channel
Goodbye System
Greet new members when they join the server with a custom welcome card or embed message!
Honeypot Channel
Honeypot Warning Message
Host exciting giveaways and create interactive polls to engage your community.
Hours
ID: 123456789
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us via our Discord support server.
Ignore Bots
Ignore Muted Members
Ignore Muted/Deafened Members
Ignore self-muted or deafened users.
Ignore Solo Members
Ignore users alone in a voice channel.
Image Card
Image URL
Immune Roles
Immune Users
in the last 24h
Inhalt
INTERACTION
Invite Unbanned Members
Italic
Join Roles
Joins / Leaves
Joins/Leaves
Kick
Kick User
Last 14 Days
Last 3 Months
Last 6 Months
Last 7 Days
Last Month
Last updated: [Date]
Last Year
Leaderboard
Level
Level ${entry.level}
Level Roles
Level System
Level Up Channel
Level Up Message
Live Preview
Loading...
Log Channels
Login with Discord
Manage modules and configurations.
Manage server currency, betting limits, daily rewards, and earning options for members.
MANAGEMENT
Master switch for all automated moderation.
Maximum amount of money allowed for gambling bets.
Media-Only Channels
Member Count
Member Flow
Members with these roles can chat without breaking count.
Members with these roles earn no XP.
Members with these roles will not be banned.
Mention Moderators
Mention Spam
Message
Message Content
Message Cooldown
Message Count (excluding Bots)
Message Mode
Message Money
Message Money Amount
Message Money Enabled
Message Roles (
Message XP
Message XP Amount
Message XP Enabled
Messages
Mobile friendly
MODERATION
Moderator Roles
Money granted per command execution.
Money granted per message.
Money granted per minute in voice channels.
Money granted per reaction.
Money Leaderboard (Auto Geld Top)
Money Multiplier
Money Multiplier (
Money Options
ms Latency
Multiple Submissions
Multiplier
New Messages
Next number expected:
No boosters configured.
No reward role
No rewards configured.
No users found on this leaderboard yet.
None (Stay in server)
Not Found
nothing it doesn't.
One-Click (Instant Verify)
Options
Orbit
Orbit Control
Orbit Dashboard
Orbit provides community management features for Discord servers, including moderation, logging, and welcome messages.
orbit-498b.onrender.com/appeal/
Overview
Prevent sending messages with exclusively capital letters.
Prevent sending messages with too many mentions.
Prevent the sending of Discord invites.
Prevent the sending of links.
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy - Orbit
Quote
Reaction Cooldown
Reaction Money
Reaction Money Amount
Reaction Money Enabled
Reaction Roles (
Reaction XP
Reaction XP Amount
Reaction XP Enabled
Reactions
Re-add on Rejoin
Ready to upgrade your server?
Real-time sync
Reset Count to 0
Reset Money On Leave
Reset XP on Ban
Reset XP on Leave
Responses that can be used when a user uses the work command.
Reward members with XP for participating in your server.
Reward Role
Role
Role Boosters (
Role-based access
Roles
Roles allowed to decide on appeals. If empty, anyone with 'Manage Messages' permission can decide.
Roles that can access the Dashboard and reset XP.
Roles that cannot be banned, kicked, or warned by Moderation commands.
Roles who are allowed to invite bots to this server without being punished.
Rollen
Rollen beim Beitritt
Rules
Save Changes
Save message
Say farewell to members when they leave the server with a custom goodbye card or embed message!
Search Messages
Select a channel...
Select a role...
Select a Server
Select category...
Select Channel...
Select Server Data
Select...
Send a message when someone boosts the server.
Send a message when someone joins.
Send a message when someone leaves.
Send Message to Channel
Send Panel
Send to channel
Send Verification Panel
Server Appeal
SERVER BOOST
Server Leaderboard - Orbit
Server Name
Server Settings
Servers
Set a custom command prefix for this server. E.g.
Set trigger words and instant bot responses. Restrict replies to specific channels.
Settings
Should members earn XP for reacting to messages?
Should members earn XP for sending messages?
Should members earn XP for using commands?
Should members earn XP while in a voice channel?
Should members get their level role back when they rejoin?
Should members keep roles below their level?
Should members keep stat roles below their count?
Should members lose all their money when leaving the server?
Should members lose their XP when they get banned?
Should members lose their XP when they leave the server?
Should members receive a server invite when their ban appeal is accepted?
Should members receive an XP boost for voting for Orbit?
Should moderators be mentioned when a new appeal is submitted?
Should moderators remain anonymous when processing appeals?
Should multiple boosters stack (add up)?
Should muted or deafened members be ignored?
Should solo members in a voice channel be ignored?
Should the default work responses be used?
Should the member's avatar be displayed in the thumbnail?
Should users be able to submit multiple appeals?
Show Avatar
Show the total number of boosts on the server
Show the total number of bots on the server
Show the total number of roles on the server
Show the total number of users on the server
Single Line Quote
Specific user IDs who will not be banned (comma-separated).
Spoiler
Stack Boosters
Stack Roles
Stack Stat Roles
Stat Cooldown
Stat Roles
Streak Bonus
Streak Limit
Strike
Submission Cooldown (Days)
Submit Appeal - Orbit
Support
Support Server
System Status
Temp Voice
Temporary Voice Channels
Terms of Service
Terms of Service - Orbit
Test Message
Text Formatting
Text outside the embed (e.g. {user_mention}).
The amount added per day past the streak limit.
The amount of days before the primary scaling stops and the flat streak bonus kicks in.
The channel where new appeals will be sent with Accept/Deny buttons.
The color of the automatic leaderboard embed.
The cooldown for the work command in minutes.
The currency symbol used in commands and responses.
The custom URL for the leaderboard. This URL must be unique.
The description text of the embed.
The instructions text displayed below the divider.
The last Discord bot
The main title of the embed sent in the ticket panel channel.
The range of money that can be earned with the work command.
The role granted upon successful verification.
The service is provided "as is". We make no warranties, expressed or implied, and hereby disclaim and negate all other warranties.
The time members must wait before submitting another appeal.
The timezone used for time-based features.
The URL where the appeal form for this server is accessible.
The warning message sent by the bot. You can use
This appeal page does not exist or is disabled.
Ticket Log Channel
Ticket Options Builder
Ticket Panel Channel
Ticket Panel Description
Ticket Panel Instructions
Ticket Panel Title
Ticket System
Tier Reward
Timeout
Timeout Penalty
Timezone
Title
to display the number of banned accounts.
to mention a channel.
Today at 12:00 PM
Top 100 Leaderboard
Total Members
Underline
Unverified Role (Remove)
Upload an image (PNG/JPG) or paste a URL to use as the boost card background.
Upload an image (PNG/JPG) or paste a URL to use as the goodbye card background.
Upload an image (PNG/JPG) or paste a URL to use as the welcome card background.
User ID
User Name
Username
Users
Users posting in this channel will be immediately banned. Ideal for catching compromised accounts.
Users Protected
Users who cannot be banned, kicked, or warned by Moderation commands.
UTC
Variables (Click to copy)
Verification
Verification Gate
Verification Mode
Verification Panel Appearance
Verified Role (Add)
Verify
Voice Hours
Voice Hours Roles (
Voice Money
Voice Money Amount
Voice Money Enabled
Voice XP
Voice XP Amount
Voice XP Enabled
Vote Boost
Warn
We collect information you provide directly to us, such as when you create or modify your account, contact customer support, or otherwise communicate with us. This includes your Discord ID, username, and server configurations.
We use the information we collect to provide, maintain, and improve our services, as well as to process transactions and send related information.
Web Dashboard
WELCOME
Welcome Cards
Welcome Channel
Welcome System
What Orbit Does
Where should the bot post the boost message?
Where should the bot post the goodbye message?
Where should the bot post the welcome message?
Which types of punishments can be appealed through this system?
Whitelist
Whitelisted Roles
Work Command Options
Work Cooldown
Work Money
x1.00
XP ${formatNumber(entry.total_xp)}
XP Multiplier
XP Options
You agree not to use the service for any unlawful purpose or in any way that interrupts, damages, or impairs the service.
You can use
You can use {variables} in the embedded message: {user_mention}, {user_globalname}, {level}, {roles}
You can use conditional scripts: {earned: Text} is displayed when any role is earned, {level[X]: Text} is shown only at Level X.
You have unsaved changes!
You must log in with Discord to submit an appeal.
Your appeal has been sent to the server moderators. They will review it shortly.
Your data is stored securely. We take reasonable measures to help protect information about you from loss, theft, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction.
